PRIYATAM KUMAR

Phone: +91-8158907736

Email: <u>kumarpriyatam191097@gmail.com</u>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/priyatam-kumar-29b75b169

IT Professional with over 5 years of experience in WEB & API Test Automation with Java, Selenium, BDD Cucumber, TestNG and Rest Assured Test Automation tools. Good knowledge & experience in WEB & API Automation framework architectures.

SKILLS

- Java
- Selenium
- Selenium WebDriver
- BDD Cucumber
- TestNG
- Maven
- Git
- Rest Assured
- SOL
- Postman

- RESTful APIs
- Jenkins
- JIRA
- AutoIT
- Core Java Script
- Jmeter
- Agile Methodology
- Dependency Injection
- Eclipse
- Intellii

EXPERIENCE

TCS PVT LTD

Test Automation Engineer (Dec 2022 – present) Bangalore, Karnataka

Workday [https://www.workday.com/]

- Workday is a cloud-based platform that's used for human capital management (HCM) and financial management.
- It helps companies manage their workforce, including payroll, benefits, performance management & leave management.
- Tested various business processes like Hire, Create Position, Job change, job profile, compensation change, worker personal data change, worker separation.
- Testing experience in workday Supervisory Organization, Subordinating Organizations, Locations, Company, Cost Centers and Workday security like Role Based Security, User Based Security, job-based security.
- Tested various compensation related scenarios like promotion, demotion, job level, job profile, grade profile change in past and future dates, and captured Impact analysis in evidence.

TECH MAHINDRA COMVIVA PVT LTD

Test Automation Engineer (June 2019 – Dec 2022) Bangalore, Karnataka

FACTOREAL [HTTPS://PRIME.FACTOREAL.INFO/]

- Factoreal is an omnichannel fan engagement automation platform that is helping sports teams connect better with their fans. Across Cricket, Football, Soccer and Baseball, Factoreal has enabled multiple teams to excel in their fan engagement and outperform all their marketing KPIs.
- API Test Automation Framework (Hybrid) developed for Factoreal API Testing using Java, Rest Assured, TestNG & Maven.
- GUI Test Automation Hybrid Framework developed for the Factoreal web application.
- Ready to run automation GUI & API regression test suite every day.
- Analyze & share the test report with the team in order to catch bugs early and raise tickets in Jira to accomplish 0 critical and 0 Blockers.

Mobilytix Reward [https://telco-stage.infinityzones.com/]

- The Mobilytix Rewards (MR) platform is an end-to-end engagement marketing solution designed to create reward-based promotional campaigns and loyalty programs.
- Aimed at enabling enterprises to achieve their business KPIs throughout the consumer's lifecycle journey.
- The platform enables brands to digitally engage with both, existing and potential customers, to ensure multiple facets. These include effective promotions, faster consumer acquisitions, upselling/cross-selling and enhancing brand loyalty.
- GUI Test Automation Framework (BDD Cucumber) developed for the Mobilytix Reward web application Using Java, Selenium, Cucumber and Maven.
- Run Automation GUI & API regression test suite every day and analyze & share the test report with the team in order to catch bugs early and raise tickets in Jira to accomplish 0 critical and 0 Blockers.

EDUCATION

NIT DURGAPUR

B.Tech (Information Technology) [2015 – 2019] Durgapur, West Bengal

HIGH SCHOOL HARNAUT

10th [2012] Harnaut, Nalanda, Bihar

R.P.S. COLLEGE

 $11^{th}-12^{th}$ [2012 - 2014] Harnaut, Nalanda, Bihar

AWARDS & ONLINE CODING PROBLEM SOLVING

- Received "Designing For Real World" winner award for Automation framework architectures.
- Received "On The Spot Award" for **Automation framework Setup** for entire team members.
- CODOLIO [https://codolio.com/profile/priyatam] Above is Codolio (All in One Coding) Portfolio tracker link which tracks my overall progress across different coding platforms like HackerRank, Leetcode, GeeksforGeeks, CodeChef.